http://www.themagiccircle.co.uk/privacy-policy

INTRODUCTION
(a)
Any personal information which is collected, gathered or processed by The Magic Circle via The Magic Circle website (“the website”) will be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
(b)
By registering to use the website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this Policy.
DATA PROTECTION REGULATIONS
(a)
The Magic Circle is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to the website. Whether you are a first-time visitor to the website or a regular user, The Magic Circle takes your privacy seriously.
(b)
We are regulated by the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR). To ensure compliance:
(i) we keep personal data up to date
(ii) we store and destroy data securely
(iii) we do not collect or retain excessive amounts of data
(iv) we protect data from loss, unauthorised use, misuse and disclosure
(c)
For the purpose of the GDPR, the data controller is The Magic Circle, 12 Stephenson Way, London NW1 2HD.
INFORMATION THAT THE MAGIC CIRCLE COLLECTS FROM YOU
(a)
The Magic Circle collects personal information from members of The Magic Circle who register with the website. This includes your name and e-mail address and other information provided at the point of application.
(b)
Instructions on how to register for member access to the website may be obtained from webmaster@themagiccircle.co.uk. Non-members cannot register.
(c)
In other cases, no personally identifiable information will be collected from you, unless you contact The Magic Circle.
(d)
If any of the information you have submitted to the website changes, please contact webmaster@themagiccircle.co.uk.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
(a)
The Magic Circle uses the information we collect from registered members in order to provide you with access to all parts of the website, to communicate with you with respect to User Name and Password changes specific to the website, and for other Magic Circle communications.
(b)
Your personal information will only be used by The Magic Circle for purposes consistent with the aims of The Magic Circle.
(c)
The Magic Circle does not share any information other than in compliance with the law. We will release personal information when required to do so by law or by any regulations and other rules to which The Magic Circle is subject.
SECURITY
(a)
The website uses a security system that protects your information from unauthorised use. However, as no data transmissions over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we cannot take responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control.
(b)
Please remember that other methods of internet communication, such as emails and messages sent via a website, are not secure unless they are encrypted. We take no responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control.
ACCESS TO YOUR DATA
Under the GDPR you may request a copy of the data that we hold about you. If you would like to do this please email secretary@themagiccircle.co.uk or write to The Secretary, The Magic Circle, 12 Stephenson Way, London NW1 2HD
Terms of UsePrivacy PolicyCookie Policy
